{
    "id": "0aeb715fc65746d9b7b8d13572637819",
    "title": "Demonstrative And Interrogative Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "………………… is that boy sitting next to Peter?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Who",
                "Which",
                "What"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3a2747899883461cb0974863c197fb42"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… was a horrible experience.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "What",
                "Which",
                "That"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "aa5881323984445993b75cd43da81162"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… are our children.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "This",
                "These",
                "What"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "522f5fb6250548599204f20059fad5b4"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… is the road that leads to the railway station?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Which",
                "Who"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5419c12c55724a948a7a68876b469f73"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… told you this story?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Who",
                "Which",
                "What"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1f7e96f4a8994bfab94d82d34cadd387"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. do you mean?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "What",
                "Which",
                "That"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8e2d1df15e824c7f9f625adfb81b9bd9"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. shall we invite to preside over the function?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Whom",
                "Which",
                "What"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e2cc8b9fbc454988aaa6054cfb87e8b3"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… is your phone?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Where",
                "Which",
                "That"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "91883e67b5904dda81d103c85e42e48f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Are the people living in a village happier than …………….. living in a town ?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "those",
                "these",
                "they"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1e146a60cefe4a628af9b372e8c77298"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… is your father?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Who",
                "Where",
                "What",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "a62464a3c73a463ea1644bdaaaf12642"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. is the house that belongs to my grandfather.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "This",
                "Which",
                "Where"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9a008a0b309b48e0995d6c6e5875db36"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………… shall we contact?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Whom",
                "What",
                "Which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "18e058dc04f54fbb871ea031393908b6"
        }
    ]
}